Guide to the Leonid N. Stolovich papers M1624
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 3. Creative works
  - Handwritten notes on philosophy, literature, art etc. (Box 126, Folder 2)
  - Survey of students on "the problem of physics and lurics": handwritten notes (Box 130, Folder 1)
- Series 4. Research works by others
  - "Uchenye Zapiski Tartuskogo Universiteta", 1991-1992 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - "Uchenye Zapiski Tartuskogo Universiteta", 1959, 1965-1966, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - "Uchenye Zapiski Tartuskogo Universiteta": off-prints (Box 155, Folder 6)
  - Off-prints, reprints of various publications (Box 155, Folder 5)
  - Tear sheets (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Tear sheets (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Tear sheets (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Subject collections. Semiotics (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - "Socio-political situation in Russia for the period mid-February 1992": Research report of the group of sociologists and political scientists (Box 94, Folders 11)
  - Abstracts of theses, sent to Stolovich: Photocopies of title pages (Box 156, Folder 2)
  - Articles, sent to Stolovich: Photocopies of title pages (Box 156, Folder 3)
  - Articles, marked by Stolovich in various publications, 1740-2006 (Box 156, Folder 4)
  - Articles, marked by Stolovich in various publications, 1740-2006 (Box 156, Folder 5)
  - Monographs and periodicals from Stolovich's library, 1886-2005: Photocopies of title pages with additional materials found there: photographs, postcards, clippings (Box 156, Folder 6)
  - Monographs and periodicals from Stolovich's library, 1886-2005: Photocopies of title pages with additional materials found there: photographs, postcards, clippings (Box 156, Folder 7)
  - Monographs and periodicals from Stolovich's library, 1886-2005: Photocopies of title pages with additional materials found there: photographs, postcards, clippings (Box 156, Folder 8)
- Series 5. Art work by others
  - Magritz, Kurt: graphic art (Flat-box 40, Folder 2)
  - Magritz, Kurt: graphic art (Flat-box 40, Folder 3)
  - Magritz, Kurt: graphic art (Flat-box 40, Folder 4)
  - Magritz, Kurt: graphic art (Box 158, Map-folder 2)
  - Ex-Librises of Tartu University and individuals (Box 119, Folder 11)
  - Ex-Librises of Tartu University by L.R. (Flat-box 152, Folder 1)
  - Fulierova, Kveta: litograph (Flat-box 152, Folder 1)
  - Sikora, Rudolf: compositions (Flat-box 152, Folder 1)
  - Chirico, Giorgio De: drawing (Flat-box 152, Folder 1)
  - Chirico, Giorgio De: catalog (Box 151, Folder 7)
  - Mavrovska, Magdalena K.: portrait of Valentic Symonovich: drawing (Flat-box 152, Folder 1)
  - Klivar, Miroslav: graphic work (Flat-box 152, Folder 1)
  - Klivar Miroslav: graphic work and catalog (Box 151, Folder 7)
  - Kudryashov, Oleg: art work (Box 159, Map-folder 3)
  - Pollu, Kaljo: graphic work (Box 155, Folder 8)
  - Art works, mostly graphics: Ferdis Kostka; Tenghiz Mirzashvili etc. (Box 151, Folder 6)
  - Art works: Tartu Ulikooli (Box 159, Map-folder 3)
  - Prints of 3 pages done on Gutenberg's machine in his museum in Mainz (Flat-box 152, Folder 1)
  - Art catalogs: Johann Heinrich Fussli (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Art catalogs: Jozef Jankovic, Valentin Levitin (Box 151, Folder 7)
  - Art catalogs: Sobi Cherif; Augusto Colombo; Alberto Sughi; Aldo Pagliacci; Amerigo Bartoli; Giuseppe Malagodi (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Art catalogs: Antonio Bini; Nina Batalli, Emanuele Cavalli, Aldo Riso; Ideas and images from Argentina (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - Art catalogs: Jiri Anderle; Aksel Eist; Luciano Minguzi; Purificato; 5 Pop in USA (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - Art catalogs: Boris Nemenskii; Giovanni Omiccioli (Box 67, Folder 11)
  - Various small art works and catalogs (Box 119, Folder 12)
  - Various small art catalogs (Box 155, Folder 8)
  - Photographs of art works: S.D. Netsvolodov, and F. Sieger (Box 151, Folder 5)
  - Posters: Valel on luhikesed jalad. Kui luhikesed 1939-1989, by Silver Wakhtre (Box 158, Map-folder 2)
  - Posters: Skoroshivatel N. 1940 by Jokubas Zove (Box 158, Map-folder 2)
  - Posters: Time (Box 157, Map-folder 1)
  - Posters: Time, 1971 (Box 158, Map-folder 2)
  - Posters: The 13th International Congress of Aesthetics, in Lahti, Finland, August, 1-5, 1995 (Box 158, Map-folder 2)
  - Posters: The 15th International Congress of Aesthetics, in Makuhari, Japan, August 27-31, 2001 (Box 157, Map-folder 1)
  - Posters: Political poster of Mikhail Bronstein (Box 159, Map-folder 3)
  - Charts: The functions of art (Box 157, Map-folder 1)
  - Charts: Graphic model of artistic activity (Box 158, Map-folder 2)
  - Photographs: The Angel's Bridge of the Toome Hill (Box 159, Map-folder 3)
  - Photographs: The City Hall in Tartu (Box 159, Map-folder 3)
  - Photographs: The Old Anatomical Theatre in Tartu (Box 159, Map-folder 3)
- Series 6. Conference materials
  - The 7th International Kant Congress in Mainz, Germany 1990 (Box 104, Folder 10)
  - The 8th International Kant Congress in Memphis, Tennessee, 1995: Correspondence (Box 128, Folder 7)
  - The 10th International Hegel Congress in Moscow, Russia, 1974 (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - The 1st Russian Congress of Philosophy in St. Petersburg, Russia, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - The 4th Russian Congress of Philosophy "Philosophy and the Future of Civilization": Moskva, 2005 (Box 137, Folder 5)
  - The 27th Congress of the Communist Party of the Soviet Union, 1986 (Box 135, Folder 5)
  - The 27th Congress of the Communist Party of the Soviet Union, 1986 (Box 135, Folder 6)
  - The 5th International Congress of Aesthetics, in Amsterdam, Netherlands, 1964, August-September: Papers, notes, newspaper clippings (Box 107, Folder 3)
  - The 5th International Congress of Aesthetics, in Amsterdam, Netherlands, 1964, August-September: Photographs, notes (Box 107, Folder 4)
  - The 6th International Congress of Aesthetics, in Uppsala, Sweden, 1968, August: Correspondence, papers, tourist guides (Box 107, Folder 6)
  - The 6th International Congress of Aesthetics, in Uppsala, Sweden, 1968, August: Papers, brochures (Box 107, Folder 7)
  - The 6th International Congress of Aesthetics, in Uppsala, Sweden, 1968, August: Papers (Box 107, Folder 8)
  - The 7th International Congress of Aesthetics, in Bucurest, Romania, 1972, August-September: Brochures (Box 105, Folder 7)
  - The 7th International Congress of Aesthetics, in Bucurest, Romania, 1972, August-September: Papers (Box 106, Folder 8)
  - The 7th International Congress of Aesthetics, in Bucurest, Romania, 1972, August-September: Newspaper clippings (Box 106, Folder 9)
  - The 7th International Congress of Aesthetics, in Bucurest, Romania, 1972, August-September: Photographs (Box 106, Folder 10)
  - The 8th International Congress of Aesthetics, in Darmstadt, Germany, 1976, August-September: Papers, correspondence, photographs, tourist guides, notes (Box 108, Folder 4)
  - The 8th International Congress of Aesthetics, in Darmstadt, Germany, 1976, August-September: Papers, correspondence, photographs, tourist guides, notes (Box 108, Folder 5)
  - The 9th International Congress of Aesthetics, in Dubrovnik, Croatia, 1980, August 25-31: Papers, photographs, tourist guides, notes (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - The 9th International Congress of Aesthetics, in Dubrovnik, Croatia, 1980, August 25-31: Papers, photographs, tourist guides, notes (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - The 12th International Congress of Aesthetics, in Madrid, Spain, September 1992: Papers, correspondence, photographs, tourist guides, notes (Box 108, Folder 1)
  - The 12th International Congress of Aesthetics, in Madrid, Spain, September 1992: Papers, correspondence, photographs, tourist guides, notes (Box 108, Folder 3)
  - The 13th International Congress of Aesthetics, in Lahti, Finland, August, 1-5, 1995: Papers, photographs, tourist guides, notes (Box 149, Folder 6)
  - The 13th International Congress of Aesthetics, in Lahti, Finland, August, 1-5, 1995: Papers, photographs, tourist guides, notes (Box 149, Folder 7)
  - The 13th International Congress of Aesthetics, in Lahti, Finland, August, 1-5, 1995: Papers, photographs, tourist guides, notes (Box 149, Folder 8)
  - The 14th International Congress of Aesthetics, in Ljubljana, Slovenia, September 1-7, 1998 (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - The 15th International Congress of Aesthetics, in Makuhari, Japan, August 27-31, 2001 (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - The 6th World Congress for Central and East European studies, in Tampere, Finland, July-August, 2000: Papers, correspondence, photographs, tourist guides, photographs, notes (Box 151, Folder 1)
  - The 6th World Congress for Central and East European studies, in Tampere, Finland, July-August, 2000:: Papers, correspondence, photographs, tourist guides, photographs, notes (Box 151, Folder 2)
  - The 6th World Congress for Central and East European studies, in Tampere, Finland, July-August, 2000:: Papers, correspondence, photographs, tourist guides, photographs, notes (Box 151, Folder 3)
  - The Philosophical and Cultural Research Centre "Eidos": conferences, symposiums (Box 137, Folder 1)
  - "Peculiarities of the artistic consciousness" III Vsemirnaia Tetralnaia Olimpiada: Moskva, 2001 (Box 137, Folder 2)
  - International Association of National Cultural Societies LUURA: conferences (Box 137, Folder 3)
  - International conference "Social memory and power": Saratov, 2002 (Box 137, Folder 4)
  - The 19th World Congress of Philosophy, in Moscow, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - The 19th World Congress of Philosophy, in Moscow, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - The 19th World Congress of Philosophy, in Moscow, 1993 (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - The 19th World Congress of Philosophy, in Moscow, 1993: Notes (Box 128, Folder 1)
  - The 20th World Congress of Philosophy, in Boston, Massachusetts, USA, August 10-16, 1998 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - The 21st World Congress of Philosophy, in Istanbul, Turkey, August 10-17, 2003 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - The 25th International Phenomenology Conference: Riga, 1990 (Box 137, Folder 6)
  - Participation in conferences, including invitations, programs (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Participation in conferences, including invitations, programs (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Participation in conferences, including invitations, programs (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Participation in conferences, including invitations, programs (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Participation in conferences, including invitations, programs (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Participation in conferences, including invitations, programs (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - The 20th World Congress of Philosophy, in Boston, Massachusetts, USA, August 10-16, 1998 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - "Aesthetic education of workers": Moscow, 1963 (Box 92, Folders 5)
  - "Art and society": Polish-Soviet Conference, Warsaw, 1974 (Box 108, Folder 2)
  - "Kultur und Kunst im ideologischen Klassenkampf": Lepzig, Germany, November 1984: Papres, notes, guides; 575th anniversary of Leipzig University (Box 113, Folder 9)
  - "Kultur und Kunst im ideologischen Klassenkampf": Lepzig, Germany, November 1984: Papres, notes, guides; 575th anniversary of Leipzig University (Box 113, Folder 10)
  - "Social determination of consciousness": Tartu, 1985 (Box 92, Folders 6)
  - Meeting of Soviet soiologists in Kiaiariku, Estonia, 1967 (Box 126, Folder 3)
  - Symposium "The problem of value in the Marxist-Leninist philosophy": Tbilisi, 1965 (Box 92, Folders 7)
  - Symposium "Sociology of art": Leningrad, November 1966 (Box 116, Folder 2)
  - The 2nd International Conference "The Jews in a changing world" in Riga, Latvia, August, 1997: Papers, correspondence, photographs, notes (Box 128, Folder 6)
  - The 3rd International Conference "The Jews in a changing world" in Riga, Latvia, October, 1999: Papers, correspondence, photographs, notes (Box 128, Folder 2)
  - The 4th International Conference "The Jews in a changing world" in Riga, Latvia, November, 2001: Papers, correspondence, photographs, notes (Box 128, Folder 3)
  - The 5th International Conference "The Jews in a changing world" in Riga, Latvia, September, 2003: Papers, photographs, notes (Box 128, Folder 4)
  - The 6th International Conference "The Jews in a changing world" in Riga, Latvia, September, 2006: Papers, correspondence, notes (Box 128, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous congresses and conferences: Programs (Box 155, Folder 7)
- Series 7. Newspapers and magazines
  - "Argumenty i fakty", 1988 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - "Argumenty i fakty", 1988 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - "Argumenty i fakty", 1989 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - "Argumenty i fakty", 1989 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - "Argumenty i fakty", 1989-1994 (Box 134, Folder 1)
  - "Argumenty i fakty", 1990 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - "Argumenty i fakty", 1990 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - "Argumenty i fakty", 1990 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - "Argumenty i fakty", 1991 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - "Argumenty i fakty", 1991 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - "Argumenty i fakty", 1992 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - "Argumenty i fakty", 1992 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - "Argumenty i fakty", 1993 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - "Argumenty i fakty", 1993 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - "Argumenty i fakty", 1994 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - "Argumenty i fakty", 1994 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - "Argumenty i fakty", 1995 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - "Argumenty i fakty" (Birzha, Moskva, Peterburg ed.), 1991-1995 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - "Alma Mater", 1990-1991 (Box 105, Folder 8)
  - "Atmoda", 1989-1990 (Box 16, Folders 13)
  - "Charka", 1994 (Box 16, Folders 32)
  - "Daidzhest", 1989-1990 (Box 17, Folders 13)
  - "Daidzhest", 1990-1991 (Box 135, Folder 2)
  - "Daidzhest", 1990-1991 (Box 135, Folder 3)
  - "Daidzhest", 1990-1992 (Box 17, Folders 14)
  - "Demokraticheskaia Rossiia", 1991 (Box 16, Folders 4)
  - "Den", 1992 (Box 16, Folders 10)
  - "Den za dnem", 1991-1997 (Box 16, Folders 27)
  - "Dvorianskii Vestnik", 2001 (Box 15, Folders 20)
  - "Edasi", 1988 (Box 19, Folders 7)
  - "Edasi", 1989 (Box 19, Folders 8)
  - "Edasi", 1989 (Box 19, Folders 9)
  - "Edasi", 1990 (Box 19, Folders 10)
  - "Edasi", "Ierusalimskie Vesti", "Soiuz","Trud", "Tartu Ulikool-TV", "Tartu Postipoiss", 1989-1990 (Box 134, Folder 2)
  - "Eesti Ekspress", 1989-1990 (Box 16, Folders 20)
  - "Eile. Tana. Homme", 1997 (Box 17, Folders 2)
  - "Ekho Litvy", 1990 (Box 20, Folders 1)
  - "Ekho Litvy", 1990 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - "Ekho Litvy", 1990 (Box 20, Folders 4)
  - "Ekho Litvy", 1990 (Box 20, Folders 2)
  - "Ekho Litvy", 1990 (Box 20, Folders 3)
  - "Estoniia", 1991 (Box 21, Folders 1)
  - "Estoniia", 1991; 1995 (Box 21, Folders 2)
  - "Estoniia", 1995 (Box 21, Folders 5)
  - "Estoniia", 1995 (Box 21, Folders 3)
  - "Estoniia", 1995 (Box 21, Folders 4)
  - "Estonia M" and its supplement "Biznes Reliz", 1995 (Box 17, Folders 12)
  - "Estoniia", "Molodezh Estonii", 1989-1991 (Box 134, Folder 7)
  - "Evreiskaia Gazeta", 1995-1996 (Box 17, Folders 11)
  - "Inkeri", 1995 (Box 16, Folders 22)
  - "Isamaaleht", 2005 (Box 16, Folders 14)
  - "Iuridicheskii Vestnik", 1994-1995 (Box 16, Folders 17)
  - "Izvestiia", 1989 (Box 138, Folder 1)
  - "Izvestiia", 1989-1990 (Box 138, Folder 2)
  - "Kaliningradskii Universitet", 1990 (Box 15, Folders 5)
  - "KESKnadal", 1999 (Box 16, Folders 28)
  - "Khashakhar": the Newspaper of Estonian Society of the Jewish Culture, 2007-2008 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - "Khashakhar"/ "Rassvet" 1988-1996 (Box 135, Folder 1)
  - "Khashakhar"/ "Rassvet", 1991-1992 (Box 15, Folders 14)
  - "Khashakhar"/ "Rassvet", 2001-2007 (Box 155, Folder 2)
  - "Khashakhar"/ "Rassvet", 2002, 2005 (Box 156, Folder 15)
  - "Kommersant", 1990 (Box 15, Folders 23)
  - "Kuranty", 1991 (Box 16, Folders 2)
  - "Laane Elu", 1989 (Box 16, Folders 31)
  - "Literaturnaia Gazeta. Dose", 1989 (Box 15, Folders 9)
  - "Literaturnaia Rossiia", 1989-1992 (Box 17, Folders 7)
  - "Masterskaia", 1989 (Box 15, Folders 13)
  - "Megapolis Express", 1993 (Box 16, Folders 11)
  - "Molodezh Estonii", 1985-1989 (Box 21, Folders 6)
  - "Molodezh Estonii", 1989 (Box 22, Folders 1)
  - "Molodezh Estonii", 1989 (Box 21, Folders 7)
  - "Molodezh Estonii", 1989 (Box 22, Folders 2)
  - "Molodezh Estonii", 1989 (Box 22, Folders 3)
  - "Molodezh Estonii", 1989-1990 (Box 22, Folders 4)
  - "Molodezh Estonii", 1990 (Box 22, Folders 7)
  - "Molodezh Estonii", 1990 (Box 23, Folders 1)
  - "Molodezh Estonii", 1990 (Box 22, Folders 6)
  - "Molodezh Estonii", 1990 (Box 23, Folders 3)
  - "Molodezh Estonii", 1990 (Box 22, Folders 5)
  - "Molodezh Estonii", 1990 (Box 22, Folders 8)
  - "Molodezh Estonii", 1990 (Box 23, Folders 2)
  - "Molodezh Estonii", 1990-1991 (Box 23, Folders 4)
  - "Molodezh Gruzii", 1989 (Box 16, Folders 6)
  - "Moskovskii Komsomolets", 1993-1996 (Box 15, Folders 17)
  - "Moskovskii Literator", 1989-1990 (Box 16, Folders 16)
  - "Moskovskii Tserkovnyi Vestnik", 1989 (Box 17, Folders 8)
  - "Moskva Nuudised", 1989 (Box 16, Folders 26)
  - "Nedelia", 1989-1990 (Box 134, Folder 6)
  - "Nedelia", weekly supplement to "Izvestiia", 1987-1988 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - "Nedelia", weekly supplement to "Izvestiia", 1990 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - "Nedelia", weekly supplement to "Izvestiia", 1989 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - "Nedelia", weekly supplement to "Izvestiia", 1989 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - "Nedelia", weekly supplement to "Izvestiia", 1990 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - "Nedelia", weekly supplement to "Izvestiia", 1990 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - "Nedelia", weekly supplement to "Izvestiia", 1990 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - "Nedelia", weekly supplement to "Izvestiia", 1991 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - "The New York Times", 1992 (Box 16, Folders 8)
  - "Nezavisimaia Gazeta", supplement "Ex Libris', 1991-1993; 2002 (Box 18, Folders 1)
  - "Noorte Haal", 1988-1989 (Box 16, Folders 23)
  - "Novaia Gazeta", 1993 (Box 16, Folders 21)
  - "Novaia Gazeta", "Russkaia pochta", "Vechernyi Tallinn", "Sovetskaia Molodezh", 1990-2001 (Box 134, Folder 3)
  - "Obshchaia Gazeta", 1996 (Box 20, Folders 5)
  - "Obshchaia Gazeta", 1996 (Box 20, Folders 6)
  - "Obshchaia Gazeta", 1996 (Box 20, Folders 7)
  - "Obshchaia Gazeta", 1998 (Box 20, Folders 8)
  - "Okna", 2006 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - "Opozitsiia", 1989 (Box 15, Folders 3)
  - "Poisk", 1990 (Box 15, Folders 19)
  - "Politika", 1980 (Box 134, Folder 8)
  - "Post", 1995 (Box 17, Folders 10)
  - "Postimees", 1991-1994 (Box 17, Folders 15)
  - "Postimees", 1996 (Box 17, Folders 16)
  - "Pravo i Pravda", 2005 (Box 17, Folders 5)
  - "Reede: Eesti Kultuurileht", 1989 (Box 15, Folders 2)
  - "Reklaam", 1988 (Box 17, Folders 1)
  - "Reshenie", 2003 (Box 16, Folders 12)
  - "Rossiiskaia gazeta", 1991 (Box 16, Folders 9)
  - "Russkaia gazeta", 1992 (Box 19, Folders 1)
  - "Russkaia gazeta", 1993 (Box 19, Folders 2)
  - "Russkaia gazeta", 1993 (Box 19, Folders 3)
  - "Russkaia gazeta", 1994 (Box 19, Folders 4)
  - "Russkaia gazeta", 1995-1996 (Box 19, Folders 5)
  - "Russkaia gazeta", 1996 (Box 19, Folders 6)
  - "Russkaia Mysl", 1995 (Box 18, Folders 5)
  - "Russkaia Mysl", 1996 (Box 18, Folders 7)
  - "Russkaia Mysl", 1996 (Box 18, Folders 4)
  - "Russkaia Mysl", 1996 (Box 18, Folders 6)
  - "Russkaia Pochta", 1993-1994 (Box 17, Folders 4)
  - "Russkii Ekspress", 1994-1995 (Box 15, Folders 24)
  - "Sankt-Peterburgskie Vedomosti", 1995 (Box 15, Folders 22)
  - "Sankt-Peterburgskii Universitet", 1992 (Box 16, Folders 5)
  - "Segodnia", 1993-1995 (Box 18, Folders 2)
  - "Segodnia", 1995-1996 (Box 18, Folders 3)
  - "Semia", 1988 (Box 15, Folders 4)
  - "Sirp ja Vasar", 1984-1989 (Box 15, Folders 1)
  - "Slovo i delo", 1992 (Box 16, Folders 15)
  - "Sobesednik", 1988-1989 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - "Sobesednik", 1989 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - "Sobesednik", 1989 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - "Sobesednik", 1990 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - "Sobesednik", 1990 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - "Sobesednik", 1990 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - "Sobesednik", 1990-1991 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - "Sobesednik", 1991 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - "Sobesednik", 1991 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - "Sobesednik", 1991 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - "Sobesednik", "Nezavisimaia Gazeta", "Sovetskaia Litvan", "Sovetskaia LAtviia", 1989-1994 (Box 134, Folder 4)
  - "Sotsiaalne Demokratia", 1990 (Box 15, Folders 15)
  - "Sovershenno Sekretno", 1989-1990 (Box 16, Folders 3)
  - "Sovetskaia Estoniia", 1985-1989 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - "Sovetskaia Estoniia", 1989 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - "Sovetskaia Estoniia", 1989 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - "Sovetskaia Estoniia", 1989 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - "Sovetskaia Estoniia", 1989 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - "Sovetskaia Estoniia", 1989 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - "Sovetskaia Estoniia", 1989-1991 (Box 134, Folder 5)
  - "Sovetskaia Estoniia", 1990 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - "Sovetskaia Estoniia", 1990 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - "Sovetskaia Estoniia", 1990 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - "Sovetskaia Estoniia", 1990 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - "Sovetskaia Estoniia", 1990 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - "Sovetskaia Estoniia", 1990 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - "Sovetskaia Estoniia", 1991 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - "Sovetskaia Estoniia", 1991 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - "Sovetskaia Estoniia", 1991 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - "Sovetskaia Estoniia", supplement "Otstavka" (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - "Sovetskaia Kultura", 1987-1988 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - "Sovetskaia Kultura", 1988 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - "Sovetskaia Kultura", 1988 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - "Sovetskaia Kultura", 1988 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - "Sovetskaia Kultura", 1988-1989 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - "Sovetskaia Kultura", 1989 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - "Sovetskaia Kultura", 1989 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - "Sovetskaia Kultura", 1989 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - "Sovetskaia Kultura", 1989 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - "Sovetskaia Kultura", 1989 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - "Sovetskaia Kultura", 1989 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - "Sovetskaia Kultura", 1989 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - "Sovetskaia Kultura", 1989-1990 (Box 134, Folder 9)
  - "Sovetskaia Kultura", 1990 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - "Sovetskaia Kultura", 1990 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - "Sovetskaia Kultura", 1990 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - "Sovetskaia Kultura", 1990 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - "Sovetskaia Kultura", 1990 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - "Sovetskaia Kultura", 1990 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - "Sovetskaia Kultura", 1990-1991 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - "Sovetskaia Molodezh", 1989 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - "Sovetskaia Molodezh", 1989-1990 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - "Sovetskaia Molodezh", 1990 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - "Sovetskaia Molodezh", 1990 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - "Sovetskaia Molodezh", 1990 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - "Sovetskaia Molodezh", 1990 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - "Sovetskaia Molodezh", 1990 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - "Sovetskaia Rossiia", 1989-1991 (Box 15, Folders 18)
  - "Sovetskii Sport", 1989 (Box 17, Folders 9)
  - "Speed-Info", 1995 (Box 16, Folders 19)
  - "Stolitsa", 1991 (Box 16, Folders 1)
  - "Die Tageszeitung", 1991 (Box 16, Folders 24)
  - "Tartu Riiklik Ulikool", 1986-1989 (Box 15, Folders 7)
  - "Tartuskii kurer", 1989 (Box 105, Folder 10)
  - "Tartuskii kurer", 1989 (Box 105, Folder 11)
  - "Televidenie", 1988-1991 (Box 15, Folders 8)
  - "Tsentr Plus", 1995 (Box 16, Folders 29)
  - "Uchitel", 1991 (Box 17, Folders 3)
  - "UFO Reviu", 1990 (Box 16, Folders 30)
  - "Universitas Tartuensis", 1989-1992, 2006 (Box 15, Folders 12)
  - "Valgaskii Arkhiv", 1994 (Box 16, Folders 7)
  - "Vechernyi Tallinn", 1989 (Box 24, Folders 4)
  - "Vechernyi Tallinn", 1990 (Box 24, Folders 5)
  - "Vechernyi Tallinn", 1990 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - "Vechernyi Tallinn", 1990 (Box 24, Folders 6)
  - "Vechernyi Tallinn", 1990 (Box 24, Folders 7)
  - "Vechernyi Tallinn", 1990 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - "Vechernyi Tallinn", 1990 (Box 24, Folders 8)
  - "Vechernyi Tallinn", 1990-1991 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - "Vechernyi Tallinn", 1991 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - "Vesti - Nedelia Plius", 1997 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - "Vestnik", 1992 (Box 16, Folders 18)
  - "Vestnik Evreiskoi Sovetskoi Kultury", 1989 (Box 16, Folders 25)
  - "Vestnik Narodnogo Fronta", 1988 (Box 15, Folders 11)
  - "Vestnik Narodnogo Fronta Estonii", 1989-1990 (Box 15, Folders 10)
  - "Vestnik Sovremennogo Iskustva Tsirk "Olimp"', 1997-1998 (Box 15, Folders 21)
  - "Vestnik Tartu", 1986 (Box 15, Folders 16)
  - "Vpered", 1986-1988 (Box 23, Folders 5)